喔 嘿 你们大家
Oh, hey, you guys?
我生日当天晚上订不到餐厅…
I couldn't get a reservation for the night of my birthday...
所以我们要改到星期四晚上
so we'll have to do dinner Thursday night instead.
- 星期四？但是那是万圣节耶   - 那又怎样？
- Thursday? But that's Halloween.     - So?
只不过是很诡异而已
It's just spooky, that's all.
那 麦克也会跟我们吃晚赛吗？
Uh, so is Mike coming to dinner?
不会 我第一次可以跟男朋友过生日 他却要上班
No. It's my first birthday with a boyfriend, and he has to work.
我很想对他发脾气 但是我想这会太快露出马脚
I'd get mad at him, but I think it's too soon to show my true colors.
那这样我会只订五个人的位子
Well, I would make the reservation for five.
我们其中一个要留下来照顾艾玛
One of us has to stay home and watch Emma.
- 我们谁该去晚餐呢？ - 瑞秋
- Which one of us should go to dinner?     - Oh, Rachel.
事实上 我想或许我们两个都可以去
Uh, actually, I was thinking maybe both of us could go.
哦 真好
Oh, yay.
谢谢 我会多用点心准备你的礼物
Thanks. I'll put a lot of extra thought into your gift.
好了 太棒了 我们全部都可以去
All right, so great, we can all go now.
真棒  嘿  你们知道吗？
That is fun. Hey. You know what?
我们六个人已经很久没有这样在一起了
We all haven't been together, the six of us, in such a long time.
你在说什么呢？我们现在就在一起啊？
What are you talking about? We're all together now.
摩妮卡 钱德并不在这里
Uh, Mon? Chandler's not here.
喔 老天
Oh, dear God.
(土尔沙)
大家好 很高兴第一次我们全员到齐
Hello, everyone. It's nice to see our team together for the first time.
现在 在我们开始之前 有任何问题吗？
Now, before we get started, are there any questions?
- 是的 肯 对吧？ - 没错
- Yes. Ken, is it?     - That's right.
听说你会来土尔沙的原因 是因为你在闲会的时候睡着…
Is it true the reason you're in Tulsa is that you fell asleep in a meeting...
然后随口就答应接下 这份你根本搞不清楚的工作 是吗？
and took the job without realizing what you were saying yes to?
嗯 别道听涂说 肯
Well, don't believe everything you hear, Ken.
但是没错 那是真的
But yeah, that's true.
好了 我们先开始看一下上一季的数字
All right, let's get started by, uh, taking a look at last quarter's figures.
克劳蒂亚 你不是应该要 先问一下老板可不可以抽烟吗？
Uh, Claudia, aren't you supposed to blow smoke up the boss's ass?
我很抱歉 你介意我抽烟吗？
I'm sorry. Does the smoke bother you?
不 我抽了好多年 然后戒了
No. I smoked for years. Then I quit.
现在也忘了为什么要戒
Right now, I can't remember why.
在办公室不准抽烟的 不是吗？
You're not allowed to smoke in this office though, right?
可以的 在奥克拉荷马…
Yes, in Oklahoma
在十五人以下的办公室 抽烟是合法的
it's legal to smoke in offices with 15 people or less.
- 你要来一根吗？ - 听着 我已经戒烟了
- Would you like one?     - All right, look. I don't smoke anymore.
如果你们其他人也想抽 请便 没关系的
But if the rest of you want to light up, go ahead, it's fine.
原来你们全部都抽烟
So you all smoke, then? Heh.
你们知道吗？我不抽烟反而看起来很没礼貌
You know, it's almost rude that I'm not smoking.
- 没那回事 如果你不想…   - 肯 拜托
- That's not true. If you don't wanna smoke...     - Ken, please!
不 不行 我不能抽烟 如果我抽烟 我老婆会杀了我
No, I can't. I can't smoke. If I smoke, my wife would kill me.
不好意思 但是你老婆不是在纽约吗？
I'm sorry, but isn't your wife back in New York?
我一直都很喜欢你 肯
I've always liked you, Ken.
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick or treat.
- 嘿   - 真是养眼啊
- Hey.     - Ooh, and "treat" it is.
哇 幸好我有换衣服
Wow. So glad I changed.
我差一点就穿上那件 连胸部都遮不住的破睡袍
I almost wore my threadbare robe that can't contain my breasts.
我不是要穿这件出门 我正在排卵…
This is not what I'm wearing. I'm ovulating...
而钱德很快就回来了 所以我想我们可以在晚餐前试一下
and Chandler's gonna be home. So I thought we would try before dinner.
喔… 等一下 这表示你们会迟到吗？
Oh. Wait, does that...? You guys won't be late for my dinner, will you?
相信我 我们已经超过一个星期没有见面了
Chandler and I have not seen each other in over a week.
我们可能会是第一个到的
We'll probably be the first ones there.
好了 待会见 祝你们搞得愉快
Okay. See you there. Happy humping.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Well hey.
哇 有人在这里抽烟吗？
Oh. Wow, somebody smoked out here?
天啊 难道他们不晓得 在公共场所是不可以抽烟的吗？
My God, don't people know you're not allowed to smoke in public spaces?
事实上 在奥克拉荷马 在少于十五人的办公室抽烟是合法的
Actually, in Oklahoma, smoking is legal in offices with fewer than 15 people.
喔 是你抽的
Oh, you smoked.
不是 我只是刚好知道 不同州的抽烟规定
No. I just happen to know a lot of trivia about smoking in different states.
例如 在夏威夷 香烟叫做雷拉纳路卡斯
For example, in Hawaii, cigarettes are called lei-lana-lukus.
喔 钱德 你身上都是臭烟味
Oh, Chandler, you stink of cigarettes.
你想摩妮卡会闻得到吗？
Do you think Monica is gonna smell it?
你在开玩笑吗？那女人的鼻子像狗一样灵
Are you kidding? That woman has the nose of a bloodhound.
胸部像希腊女神一样美
And the breasts of a Greek goddess.
菲比？
Pheebs?
我要走了
I'm gonna go.
好了 有什么可以掩盖味道
Okay. Something to cover the smell.
炉灶清洁剂
Oven cleaner.
无添加香味
Unscented.
欢迎回来
Welcome home.
我好想你
I've missed you.
- 想要跟我进房间吗？ - 不 谢了 不用
- You wanna join me in the bedroom?     - No, thanks, I'm good.
好的 你想要这样玩 是吗？
Oh, okay. So you want to play it that way, do you?
嗯 你知道吗？事实上 我才刚下飞机…
Well, uh, you know what? Actually, I just got off a plane...
觉得有点脏 我应该先洗个澡
so I'm feeling gross. Maybe I should take a shower.
- 过来 你不需要洗澡   - 好的 事实上是…
- Come here, you don't need a shower.     - All right, the truth is...
我在乱流的时候弄脏了自己
I soiled myself during some turbulence.
什么味道？我闻到烟味
What do I smell? I smell smoke.
你有抽烟吗？
Did you smoke?
有 但是只抽了一根
Yes. But I just had one.
两根
Two.
两小根 好吧 五根
Two tiny cigarettes. Okay, five.
一包 两包… 一条
A pack. Two pack... A carton.
两天抽三大条香烟
Three big fat cartons in two days.
但是都结束了 我已经决定 再也不要抽烟了
But it's over. I've made a decision, I'm not gonna smoke anymore.
嗯 那是要送给你的
Well, those are for you.
好的 嗯 到时候见 拜
All right. Well, we'll just, uh, see you when you get here. Bye.
喔 那是我妈 她遇到大塞车
Oh, that was my mom. She's stuck in terrible traffic.
这是第三个征兆 告诉我不应该离开艾玛
Okay, well, that is now the third sign that I should not leave Emma.
- 另外两个征兆是什么呢？ - 嗯 第一个是 我不想要
- What are the other two?     - Well, the first one is, I don't want to.
第二个是 我不要去
And second one, I'm not going.
我知道这是我们第一次离开艾玛
I know this is the first time we're leaving the baby.
我知道这对你很困难 但是…
Hey, I know how hard it is for you. But...
但是一切都会很好的 我是说 我妈会在这里照顾她
But everything's gonna be fine. I mean, my mom is gonna be with her.
- 她很会照顾小孩的   - 真的吗？
- She's great with kids.     - She is?
真的
Yeah.
那摩妮卡呢？
What about Monica?
你都只听她说的话 那个肥妹是个恐怖分子
Hey, you only hear Monica's side of that. Okay, that little fatso was a terror.
我只是不认为我办得到
I just don't think I can do it.
你知道吗？你应该 也办得到
You know what? You can and you should.
真的 这对你会有帮助的
Really, it'll be good for you.
事实上 你知道吗？
In fact, you know what?
你何不先去餐厅 我留下来等我妈…
Why don't you go ahead to the restaurant, and I will wait for my mom...
然后我再过去找你们 真的 你应该过去 出去
...and then I'll meet you there? No, no, really, you should go. Go out.
真的 这世界是你的 甩开高跟鞋 挥洒出自己的颜色
Really, the world is your oyster. Kick up your heels. Paint the town red.
你是该学些新的广告词
You need to learn some new slang.
我是说真的 走吧 你该走了
I'm serious. Come on, you should go.
来 去吧
Here. No, just go.
- 那   - 不 不  你知道吗？
- Well... Oh!     - No, no. You know what?
你别想要进去  宝宝没事的 现在快走吧
You're not getting back in there. The baby's fine. Now, scram.
什么都别惊 向前行
Yeah, tell your story walking.
我只是要说 我忘记带钥匙了
I was just going to say that I left my keys.
哦
Oh.
老天啊 这下我们惨了
Holy moley, are we in a pickle now.
他们人呢？已经迟到四十分钟了
Where is everyone? They're 40 minutes late.
- 我知道   - 我饿死了
- I know.     - I'm starving.
我知道我们今晚要来这里 所以我整天都没有吃东西
I knew we were coming here tonight. I ate nothing all day.
那我怎么说呢？我才吃一顿午餐而已
What about me? I only had one lunch today.
那么 其他的贵宾很快就会到吗？
So are we expecting the rest of our party shortly?
是的 我们衷心期盼他们的即将到临 是啊
Yes, they are expected presently. Yeah.
他们即将现身了
Their, um... Their arrival is in the offing.
好的 我们也有两人座的位置
Right. We do have a table for two available.
- 或许你们…   - 不用了 他们要来了
- Perhaps you'd be...     - No, they're coming.
我们就在这里等
We're waiting right here.
乔瑟夫
Joseph.
没有您需要担心 他们应该不会太漫长
One needn't worry. They shan't be long.
我们有一些人在等着要用餐
It's just that we do have some large parties waiting.
喔  您真的 需要这样机机车车的吗？
Oh, one really does have a stick up one's ass, doesn't one?
什么时代了怎么还抽烟呢？你没有看过反烟广告吗？
How can you smoke in this day and age? Have you not seen that ad? Huh?
那个小孩走穿过他爷爷那个广告 真是吓死人了
Where the little kid walks through Grandpa? It's chilling.
我搞砸了 不过是一个会议 每个人都在抽烟啊
I messed up. It was a meeting. Everybody was smoking.
那又如何？你难道没有任何意志力吗？
So what? Don't you have any willpower?
意志力？我看过你在吃巧克力的家庭录影带…
Willpower? I've watched home movies of you eating Ding Dongs...
连包装纸都来不及打开
without taking the tinfoil off.
你说那看起来很性感
You said that was sexy.
好了 好了 可不可以算了？我不会再抽烟了
Okay, look, can we just drop this? I'm not gonna smoke again.
没错 因为我禁止你抽烟
That's right, because I forbid you to smoke again.
- 你禁止我？ -嗯
- You forbid me?     - Mm-hm.
我大老远飞回来见我可爱的老婆
You know, I've flown a long way to see my loving wife.
对了 她在吗？
Is she here, by the way?
钱德 别开玩笑 好吗？我现在非常非常地不高兴
Chandler, don't joke with me. Okay? I'm very, very upset right now.
- 现在是你最不高兴的时候吗？ - 我想应该是的
- Oh. Would you say this is the most upset you could be?     - I think so.
那 我何不就…
Well, then I might as well...
这样做
do this.
不确定接下来要干嘛
Not really sure what to do now.
我告诉你我们要做什么
I'll tell you what we're gonna do.
我们要去参加菲比的生日晚餐 我们已经迟到了
We're already late for Phoebe's birthday dinner.
所以你要把香烟熄掉…
So you're going to put out that cigarette...
我们先暂停吵架 先上床再说
we're gonna put this fight on hold, and go have sex.
好 什么？
Fine. What?
上床  今天是我排卵的最后一天 如果我们不做…
Sex. This is the last day I'm ovulating. If we don't do it...
我们就要等到下个月了
we're gonna have to wait until next month.
你是认真的吗？
You're serious?
- 喔 是的   - 随便 做就做 但我不跟你说话
- Oh, yeah.     - All right, fine, I'll do it, but no talking.
- 而且没有抱抱   - 而且不亲吻你脖子
- And no cuddling.     - And no kissing your neck.
喔 很好  反正我也很讨厌你那样做
Oh, good. I hate it when you do that.
那我要尽量亲你的脖子
And lots of kissing your neck.
嗯 管理员不在家
Okay, well, the super's not home.
但是我妈快到了 她有钥匙
But my mother's gonna be here, and she has the key.
我等不了那么久 你得想想办法 把门撞破吧
I can't wait that long. You have to do something. Knock that door down.
我也想 但是我就跟桃子一样容易撞伤
I would, but I bruise like a peach.
而且 你知道一切都会没事的 婴儿在睡觉
Besides, you know, everything's gonna be fine. The baby's sleeping.
- 万一她跳出摇篮呢？ - 根本连头都抬不高 还想跳
- What if she jumps out of the bassinet?     - Can't hold her own head up.
但是  跳了
But, yeah, jumped.
喔 天啊  我水龙头还开着
Oh, my God. I left the water running.
瑞秋 你没有让水龙头开着 拜托 冷静一点 好吗？
You did not leave the water running. Please, pull yourself together, okay?
那 我有把炉子开着吗？
Well, did I leave the stove on?
1996年之后你就没有煮过饭了
You haven't cooked since 1996.
窗户有开着吗？如果开着 鸟可能会飞进来然后…
Is the window open? If the window's open a bird could fly in and...
天啊 你知道吗？我想你说对了
Oh, my God, you know what? I think you're right.
- 听   - 什么？什么？
- Listen.     - What? What?
是鸽子 不 等等 不 是老鹰飞进去了
A pigeon. No. No, wait, no. An eagle flew in.
飞到炉子上然后烧了起来了
Landed on the stove and caught fire.
婴儿看到这一切 从公寓这边跳过去帮助老鹰
The baby, seeing this, jumps across the apartment to the mighty bird's aid.
而老鹰却误判认为 这是个攻击的行动…
The eagle, however, misconstrues this as an act of aggression...
用爪子捉住婴儿
and grabs the baby in its talon.
就在这时候 水龙头的水 充满了整间公寓
Meanwhile, the faucet fills the apartment with water.
婴儿跟老鹰还在激战中 双方被死亡的陷阱困住…
Baby and bird, still ablaze, are locked in a death grip...
在公寓内的漩涡里旋转着
swirling around the whirlpool that fills the apartment.
天 如果这一切是真的你就死定了
Boy, are you gonna be sorry if that's true.
- 哈罗   - 嗨
- Hello.     - Hi.
已经一个小时了
It's been an hour.
经理要我问你们是否考虑换到小桌子
The maitre d' asked if you'd reconsider switching to a smaller table.
或许我们应该先用餐
Maybe we should just eat now.
在人还没有到齐之前你们不能点餐 这是餐厅规定
You can't order until the entire party's arrived. Restaurant policy.
好 那如果说另一桌离开了…
Well, how about this? Another table leaves, right...
但是他们的餐盘里还有食物…
but there's still some food left on their plates.
餐厅有规定不能吃那些食物吗？
Okay, what's the restaurant's policy about people eating that?
- 那是很不合适的   - 但是还是会发生啊
- It's frowned upon.     - But it happens.
- 好了 我要去厕所   - 你不能去
- All right, I gotta go to the bathroom.     - No, you can't go.
不 不 不 我没有办法自己保住这张桌子
No, no, no. I can't hold this table on my own.
如果他们要我换位子 我会屈服的
If they ask me to move, I'll cave.
如果你要我留下来 我会尿裤子的
Well, if you ask me to stay, I'll pee.
晚安 小姐
Good evening, miss.
小姐？
Miss?
小姐？小姐？
Miss? Miss?
好了 算了 我换位子 好了 你不需要动手动脚的
Okay, fine, I'll move. All right. You don't have to manhandle me.
- 哪里？ - 好的
- Where?     - Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
哇
Wow.
你们终于到了
Finally, you guys made it.
菲比 这些人是谁…？
Pheebs, who the hell...? Ah!
多花点时间在领带上 那样可以生出小孩来
Spend more time with the tie. That'll make a baby.
听着 我做不到 我没有办法在吵架的时候还跟你做爱
Look, I can't do this. I can't make love to you while we're fighting this way.
喔 是啊 现在你可真敏感纤细
Oh, sure. Now you're Mr. Sensitivity.
那当初你想在我叔叔丧礼之后做爱时…
But when you wanted to have sex right after my uncle's funeral...
那是庆祝生命
That was a celebration of life.
好了 我不想这样做
All right, look, I'm not gonna do this.
你想要我们的孩子 在这种情况下受孕吗？
Is this the way you want our baby to be conceived?
不 你是对的
No, you're right.
我们不应该在这种情况下做
Yeah, we shouldn't do it like this.
反正 我很抱歉
For what it's worth, I'm sorry.
我不应该对你抽烟的事这样刁难
I shouldn't have come down on you so hard about the smoking.
你是抽了几根烟 又不代表世界末日
So you had a few cigarettes. It's not the end of the world.
- 真的？ - 是的
- Really?     - Yeah.
你真不可思议
You are incredible.
听着 我不会再抽烟了
And listen, I'm not gonna smoke again.
如果我抽 我保证也会 隐藏到让你看不出来
And if I do, I promise I will hide it so much better from you.
- 想吗？ - 我们来庆祝生命
- Do you want to?     - Yeah, let's celebrate life.
好
Okay.
喔 天啊
Oh, God.
喔 感谢上帝你没事
Oh, thank God you're okay.
我很抱歉我们离开你 妈咪再也不会离开你了
I'm sorry we left you. Mommy will never leave you again.
再也… 再也不会了
Never, ever, ever again.
太棒了 我们走吧
Great. So let's get going.
我是说真的 在经历过刚刚的事之后 我再也不会离开她了
Oh, no. I mean it. After what just happened, I'm never leaving her again.
我了解 分离是很煎熬的
I understand. Separation is hard.
有一次我要离开罗斯去美容院
One time I was about to leave Ross to go to the beauty parlor.
他就变得很不开心 他把衣服脱光…
And he got so upset he took off all his clothes...
把小鸡鸡夹在双腿间…
tucked his willy between his legs...
然后哭喊〞妈咪 我是女生 带我跟你去〞
and cried out, "Mommy, I'm a girl. Take me with you."
物换星移之后 跟你分开已经变得容易很多了
Somehow, over time, it got easier to be apart from you.
啊
Ah.
不客气
You are welcome.
- 你知道吗？我们还是不要说话   - 什么？
- You know what? Let's not talk.     - What?
我对你抽烟的事还是很生气
I am still so mad at you for smoking.
但你说你已经原谅我了
But you said you forgave me.
只不过是几根烟 没有什么大不了的
It was just a couple of cigarettes, no big deal.
喔
Oh, blah-blah-blah-blah.
我会这么说是因为我正在排卵
I was ovulating
而你却说如果我们在吵架 你就不会跟我做爱
and you said you wouldn't have sex with me if we were fighting.
- 你骗我跟你上床？ - 没错 我得到我想要的了
- You tricked me to get me into bed?     - That's right. I got mine.
我被利用了
I feel so used.
我想他们不会来了 你想要点了吗？
Well, I guess they're not coming. You want to just order?
谢谢
Thank you.
侍者？好了 我会说很快 所以记好
Waiter? All right, this is gonna go fast, so try to keep up.
意大利扁面配松露切片 然后肋跟牛排…
Risotto with shaved truffles and the rib steak...
加上酥炸鸡油结和波尔多红酒酱…
with the golden chanterelles and the Bordelaise sauce...
希望我以上说的那么多东西 没有包括〞蜗牛〞
unless any of that stuff I just said means "snails."
- 是没有   - 蕃茄馅饼
- It does not.     - Tomato tart...
你建议哪种面呢？
and, um, which of the pastas would you recommend?
- 嗯 两种都很美味…   - 两种都要 谢谢
- Oh, well, they're both exquis...     - Both it is. Thank you.
喔 我可以有个特殊要求吗？
Oh, uh, can I make a special request?
你可以全部一起上吗？
Can you bring everything as soon as it's ready?
前菜 前餐 我们不介意
Appetizers, entrees, we don't care.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hi. Hi.
- 我可以等你们加点   - 你们迟到一个多小时了
- I'll just wait to put your order in.     - You guys are over an hour late.
- 发生了什么事？ - 很抱歉
- What happened to you two?     - So sorry.
我们被锁在公寓外面
We got locked out of the apartment.
真是好借口 可以给我吃吗？
That's a great story. Can I eat it?
然后瑞秋在犹豫是不是要离开婴儿
And then Rachel wasn't sure she could leave the baby.
不是很容易 但是今天是你生日 我做了我必须要做的事
It wasn't easy, but it's your birthday and I did what I had to do.
那是茱蒂跟艾玛在吧台那边吗？
And that's Judy over there at the bar with Emma?
这是最好的方式 这样我才不会分心 担心艾玛…
This is for the best. I'm not distracted, worrying about Emma...
在家有没有事 我得要完全跟你们待在这里
how she's doing at home, and I'm gonna be completely here with you.
- 喔 她吐了 她吐了   - 什么？
- Oh, she spit up.     - What?
茱蒂？她吐 茱蒂 醒醒 茱蒂
She spit up. Judy? She spit... Judy, look alive, Judy.
- 谢谢   - 谢谢
- Thank you.     - Thanks.
喔 每道菜看起来都很美味
- Ooh.     - Whew, everything looks delicious.
我应该点什么呢？我应该点什么呢？
What should I have? What should I have?
不能打女人 不能打女人
Never hit a woman. Never hit a woman.
我知道你的意思 菜单实在太棒了
I know what you mean, this looks incredible.
罗斯像桃子一样容易受伤 他像桃子一样容易受伤
Ross bruises like a peach. He bruises like a peach.
好了 我要点无花果沙拉 还有鸭肉
Okay, I'll have the fig salad and the duck.
我要点汤跟鲑鱼
I'll have the, uh, soup and the salmon.
记住 先做好的就先出 好吗？
Remember, whatever comes up first, okay?
- 快点…   - 生日快乐
- And hurry...     - Happy birthday.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
- 你们去哪了？ - 嗯 我们刚刚在吵架
- Where have you been?     - Well, we had a little fight.
我怎样都不会骗人上床
I would never lie to get someone into bed.
你曾经骗过女生 说你是甘乃迪家族的人
You used to tell girls you were a Kennedy.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢 哇
Thanks. Wow.
有点挤 不是吗？你为什么不订大一点的桌子呢？
A little tight, isn't it? Why didn't you get a bigger table?
你有订 但他们要你换桌
You had a big table but they made you move.
闭嘴 摩妮卡
Ha, ha. Shut up, Monica.
嗯 我想钱德应该想要点烟燻鸭肉
Oh, well, I suppose that Chandler will have the smoked duck.
而我想摩妮卡应该想点酥炸鼠肉
And I suppose that Monica will have the manipulative shrew.
- 我再让你们考虑一下   - 什么？你要去哪？
- I'll give you another minute.     - What, where you going?
他说她想要鼠肉的
He said she wanted the shrew.
瑞秋 别这样 艾玛没事的
Rach, come on, Emma's fine.
你已经变成过分关心的母亲了 你要停止这样
You're turning into an obsessive mother, okay? You need to stop.
你们有听过罗斯他妈 去美容院的故事吗？
You guys ever hear the story about when Ross' mom went to the beauty salon?
- 你是说小鸡鸡的事吗？ - 他们早就知道了
- You mean the willy story?     - Ha, ha. They already know it.
我们等你们好久了
We've been waiting for you for a long time.
- 你们应该点餐了   - 没关系
- Maybe you should order.     - That's okay.
- 我告诉侍者他们要点什么了   - 你为什么那样做呢？
- I told the waiter what they want.     - Why would you do that?
钱德 控制一下你的女人
Chandler, control your woman.
好了 嗯… 既然大家都已经点餐了
Okay, well... Everybody has ordered.
我想要先敬菲比一杯 来开始今晚的庆祝
I would like to start the celebration and make a toast to Phoebe.
- 她袜子掉了   - 什么？
- She dropped her sock.     - Aw. What?
- 不 不 艾玛的袜子掉了   - 妈在这里？
- No. No, Emma dropped her sock.     - Mom's here?
我今天想跟她一起用午餐 她告诉我她不在附近
I wanted to have lunch with her today. She told me she was out of town.
罗斯 她还是没有注意到 婴儿的袜子已经在地上了
Ross, she still has not noticed that the baby's sock is on the ground.
真是敬的好
It's a good toast.
听着 你可不可以叫她呢？
Look, will you please get her attention?
妈咪？
Mommy?
喔 天啊 茱蒂 把袜子捡起来
Oh, for God's sake, Judy, pick up the sock.
捡起袜子  捡起袜子
Pick up the sock! Pick up the sock!
我很抱歉 这样很没礼貌吗？
I'm sorry, was that rude?
我这样的吼叫…
Did my little outburst...
有使今晚 变得比较难堪吗？
...blunt the hideousness that is this evening?
听着 我知道你们都有自己的事…
Look, I know you all have a lot going on...
但我想要的只不过是跟我的朋友 一起吃晚餐庆祝我的生日
but all I wanted to do was have dinner with my friends on my birthday.
你们全部都迟到 而且连打电话告知的礼貌都没有
And you are all so late, and you didn't even have the courtesy to call.
已经来不及了
Well, it's too late now.
菲比 我想那应该不是我们
Yeah, Pheebs, I don't think that's us.
喔 那 这个…还没有完 喂？
Oh, well, this is... This is not over. Hello?
- 你们俩是怎么回事呢？ - 喔 是这样的 我正在排卵
- What is going on with you two?     - Well, you see, I'm ovulating.
喔 是啊 她总是那样说
Oh, yeah, that's what she says.
或许你根本没有在排卵 或许那只是要拐我上床的借口
But maybe you're not ovulating at all. Maybe it's a clever ruse to get me into bed.
是啊 烟虫 就是那样没错 我就是很想要
Yeah, Smokey, that's what it was. I just can't get enough.
你们不会相信的
You're not gonna believe this. She lied.
她竟然骗我跟她上床
She tricked me into having sex with her.
所以呢？你做爱了 不是吗？
So? You got to have sex, right?
我是怎么了？像女生爱发牢骚
What's the matter with me? Why am I such a girl?
- 好了 那是麦克   - 喔 菲比 亲爱的 我们很抱歉
- Okay. That was Mike.     - Oh, Phoebe, honey, we are so sorry.
你说的对极了 我们在这里会全心全意…
You are totally right. We are here 100 percent...
而且我们爱你 我们已经准备好要开始庆祝你的生日了
and we love you, and we are ready to start your birthday celebration.
你们 这对我实在太意义重大了
Oh. You guys, that means the world to me.
好了 我要走了
Okay, I'm gonna take off.
什么？
What?
我也爱你们 但是 麦克提早下班了
Oh, I love you guys too, but Mike got off work early.
等等
Wait.
等等 我不是那种会抛下朋友…
Wait. I'm not the... I'm not the kind of girl that just ditches her friends...
见色忘友的人
to be with her boyfriend.
你们知道吗？事实上我是…
You know what? I am.
再见 大家 茱蒂  再见
Bye, guys. Judy. Bye.
如果菲比走了 我们可以 带艾玛回家吗？
Oh, thank God. If Phoebe's gone, can we take Emma home?
好主意 我们的保姆刚才又点了一杯白酒
That's a good idea. Our babysitter just pounded another chardonnay.
- 再见   - 再见
- Bye, you guys.     - Bye.
再见 我想就只剩下我们了
See you. Well, I guess it's just us.
我或许还在排卵 你还想再试试看吗？
So I'm probably still ovulating. Do you wanna give it another try?
你从没有跟甘乃迪家的人上过床吗？
So you've never had sex with a Kennedy, have you?
- 你们不会就这样跑去做了吧？ - 我们时间不多了
- You're gonna go do it?     - We don't have much time.
一但卵子进入输卵管…
Once the egg descends into the fallopian tube...
喔 等等… 滚吧
Whoa, whoa, get out of here.
我诚挚地希望你的朋友会回来
I sincerely hope the rest of your party is returning.
不 只剩下我一个人
No, just me. All alone.
六人份晚餐全给我一个人
Dinner for six for one.
很好 你们将会目睹到 一个非常特别的表演
Well, you boys are about to see something really special.
- 切都还好吗？ - 棒极了
- How was everything, sir?     - Excellent.
特别是鼠肉 真是美味
The shrew, in particular, was exquisite.
我希望你还有胄口
Well, I hope you've got some room left.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快乐 亲爱的…
Happy birthday, dear
乔伊
Joey. Joey.
Joey
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
这是最棒的生日了
This is the best birthday ever.